Social Welfare, School of; Records ua690
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Faculty, 1965-1997; Undated; 4; 2.3 cubic ft.
  The bulk of the records consist of faculty meeting minutes and agendas from 1965-1996 with a gap in records from 1972-1976. Also included are copies of minutes and agendas that are annotated by the current dean. Minutes and agendas include supporting documents used in the meetings, as well as correspondence and memoranda from the dean relating to issues raised in meetings or to be considered at future meetings. Other materials include yearly faculty activity reports that outline scholarship and service completed by faculty as well as materials related to summer faculty retreats including correspondence, planning documents, and materials generated at the retreat.
  - Faculty Meeting Narrative, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 1)
  - Faculty Meeting Narrative, 1967-1969 (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 2)
  - Faculty Meeting Narrative, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 3)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1976 (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 4)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1977; Undated (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 5)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1978; Undated (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 6)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1979; Undated (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 7)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1980; Undated (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 8-9)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1981; Undated (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 10-11)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1982; Undated (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 12-13)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1983; Undated (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 14)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1984; Undated (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 15-16)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1985; Undated (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 17-18)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1986; Undated (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 19-20)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1987; Undated (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 21-22)
  - May 1, 1987 - April 30, 1988 Faculty Activity Reports (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 23)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1988; Undated (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 24-25)
  - 8/27/93 Faculty Retreat, 1988; 1993; Undated (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 26-27)
  - 1988 - 1989 Faculty Activity Reports (1 of 2 folders), Undated (Box 1 (4-Faculty), Folder 28-29)
  - 1988 - 1989 Faculty Activity Reports (2 of 2 folders), Undated (Box 2 (4-Faculty), Folder 1)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1989; Undated (Box 2 (4-Faculty), Folder 2-3)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (4-Faculty), Folder 4-5)
  - May 1, 1989 - April 30, 1990 Faculty Activity Reports, Undated (Box 2 (4-Faculty), Folder 6-7)
  - 8/27/91 Faculty Retreat, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 2 (4-Faculty), Folder 8-9)
  - May 1, 1990 - April 30, 1991 Faculty Activity Reports (Box 2 (4-Faculty), Folder 10-11)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1991; Undated (Box 2 (4-Faculty), Folder 12-15)
  - May 1, 1991 - April 30, 1992 Faculty Activity Reports, Undated (Box 2 (4-Faculty), Folder 16-17)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1992; Undated (Box 2 (4-Faculty), Folder 18-19)
  - 8/28/92 Faculty Retreat, 1992; Undated (Box 2 (4-Faculty), Folder 20)
  - 8/28/92 Faculty Retreat Brainstorm Boards, 1992 (Flat-file 1)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1993; Undated (Box 2 (4-Faculty), Folder 21)
  - Faculty Retreat, 1994 (Box 2 (4-Faculty), Folder 22)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1994; Undated (Box 2 (4-Faculty), Folder 23-24)
  - 8/24/95 Faculty Retreat, 1994; Undated (Box 2 (4-Faculty), Folder 25-26)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1995; Undated (Box 3 (4-Faculty), Folder 1)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1996; Undated (Box 3 (4-Faculty), Folder 2)
  - 9/18/96 Faculty Retreat, 1996; Undated (Box 3 (4-Faculty), Folder 3-4)
- Subject Files, 1964-1999; Undated; 5; 7 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Subject Files contain the day-to-day working files of the School of Social Welfare. Correspondence and memoranda, primarily from the dean at the time relating to various topics within the files, are interspersed throughout. Included among the materials are enrollment and admissions data, three and five year plans on the development and management of the school, publications, bulletins, commencement programs and speeches, grant proposals, committee membership and reports, and year-end reports from programs within the School of Social Welfare. Grant proposals include information relating to the proposed Social Work Research Development Center. School Bulletins range from 1965 through 1979. Materials relating to the Council on Social Work Education (CSWE) include statistical reports and the involvement of Lynn Videcka-Sherman as a board member on the council. Also included are scrapbook materials containing newspaper clippings, information on alumni and student achievements, and a few photos, primarily taken of faculty members. General files from the Continuing Education Program (CEP) are included within this series as well. Please note that not all dates are inclusive.
  - Ad Hoc Committee on the Center for Social Work Research Practice, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Ad Hoc Committees, 1988-1990; 1997; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Administration/Supervision Concentration - Task Force Recommendation, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Administrative Self-Study, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Admissions and Recruitment Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - 1990 - 1995 Admissions Information - [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Admissions Procedures, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Admissions Reports, 1973-1974; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Alumni Newsletter and Communications, 1984-1986; 1990-1996; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9-10)
  - Alumni Newsletter Submissions, 1989-1993; 1996-1997; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11-12)
  - Alumni Survey, 1976 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Annie E. Casey Foundation Projects, 1990-1992; 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14-15)
  - 25th Anniversary Convocation and Reunion Dinner, 1983; 1989-1991; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16-17)
  - Application for Admission to Graduate Study, 1964; 1977; 1983-1984; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Awards for Excellence, 1985-1987; 1990-1991; 1993; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Bachelor of Social Work Program Data - [RESTRICTED], 1994-1996; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Bulletins, 1965-1969 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Bulletins, 1965-1971 (Oversized 1)
  - Bulletins, 1970-1972 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Bulletins, 1973-1975; 1977 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Bulletins, 1978 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Bulletins - Continuing Education Project, 1976-1979 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Bylaws, 1971-1995; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 26-27)
  - Camp Liberty - [RESTRICTED], 1990-1992; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - A Celebration of Literacy - Student Writings, 1987 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - CEP Account Information Abstracts, 1978-1981; 1989-1990 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - CEP Adjunct Instructors, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - CEP Audit, 1981; 1983 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - CEP Certificates of Participation, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - CEP Child and Family Services Training Project Agendas, 1976 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - CEP Correspondence and Memoranda, 1985-1987; 1993; 1996; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - CEP Cost Sharing, 1978-1982; 1986 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - CEP Course 1 Module 2 - Performance Improvement, 1975; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - CEP Course 4 Module 2 - Organizational Change, 1967; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - CEP Course Offerings in Buffalo, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - CEP Course Registration for Department of Social Services Employees, 1983; 1989 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - CEP Current Issues in Social Services - Prepared for Internal Use, 1976 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - CEP Discretionary Salary Increases, 1981; 1985-1986 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - CEP Graduate and Undergraduate Course Offerings, 1981-1986; 1988-1989 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - CEP Monthly Management Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8-9)
  - CEP School Advisory Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - CEP Spring 1987 Graduate and Undergraduate Course Offerings (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - CEP Training Proposal, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - CEP Workshop Brochures and Registration Forms, 1979-1984 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - CEP Workshops for Public Agencies and Human Service Professionals, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Chancellor's Social Service Task Force Communications, 1991-1993; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15-18)
  - 1984 Commencement (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - 1989 Commencement, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - 1990 Commencement, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - 1991 Commencement, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - 1992 Commencement - [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - 1993 Commencement, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - 1994 Commencement, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - 1995 Commencement - [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - 1996 Commencement, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - 1997 Commencement - [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Commencement Honors Convocation Script, 1992; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Committee Elections, 1980-1981; 1984-1989; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 30-31)
  - Committee Membership, 1980-1998; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 32-33)
  - Committee on Admissions and Recruitment, 1983-1984; 1986-1989; 1992-1994; 1996; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - 1990 - 1991 Committee Year-End Reports, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - 1991 - 1992 Committee Year-End Reports, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - 1992 - 1993 Committee Year-End Reports, Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - 1993 - 1994 Committee Year-End Reports, Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - 1994 - 1995 Committee Year End Reports, Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - 1995 - 1996 Committee Year-End Reports, Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - 1996 - 1997 Committee Year-End Reports, Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - 1997 - 1998 Committee Year-End Reports - [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Community and Social Service Program, 1977; 1988-1989; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Community Service Program History, 1970-1971; 1973; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Community Service Program Memoranda and Correspondence, 1970; 1972; 1975 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Community Service Program Student Evaluations of Program, 1974 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Community Service Program Student Volunteers Publications, 1973-1974; 1977; 1979-1983; 1985-1986; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11-12)
  - Community Service Sticker, 1977 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Conference Invitations, Announcements, and Programs, 1975; 1983; 1986; 1989; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Council of Community Service Awards, 1992-1993; 1996; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15-16)
  - Council of Community Services Board of Directors, 1992-1997; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 17-18)
  - Council of Deans, 1990-1996; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Course Requirements Volunteer Opportunities and Agencies, ca. 1973 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - CSWE Accreditation, 1990-1993; 1996; 1998; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - CSWE Annual Statistical Report of Registered Students - [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - CSWE Annual Statistical Reports - [RESTRICTED], 1977-1984; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - CSWE Annual Statistical Reports - [RESTRICTED], 1985-1989; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24-25)
  - CSWE Annual Statistical Reports - [RESTRICTED], 1990-1991; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - CSWE Board and Commission, 1993 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - CSWE Curriculum and Policy Statement, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - CSWE Elections, 1991; 1994; 1996; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - CSWE Faculty Development and Program Planning Committee, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - CSWE Millennium Project, 1996 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - CSWE Memoranda and Communications, 1989; 1991-1997; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - CSWE National Legislative Committee, 1985; 1987 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - CSWE Site Visit: BYU and LSU, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Curriculum and Educational Policy Committee Communications, 1978-1985; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 35-36)
  - Curriculum and Educational Policy Committee Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1979-1990; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 37-40)
  - Curriculum and Educational Policy Committee Operating Procedures, 1981 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Day Care for the Abused/Neglected Child, Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Degrees Awarded, 1989-1990; 1992; 1995-1996; 1998; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Department of Social Services Total Quality Initiative, 1993 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Dual Jointly Registered Master's Program in Sociology and Social Work for New Paltz and Albany - Proposal and Planning Communications, 1980-1996 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2-5)
  - 1989 - 1990 Enrollment Data, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - 1991 Enrollment Data, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - 1993 Enrollment Data (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - 1994 Enrollment Data - [RESTRICTED], 1994-1995 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - 1995 Enrollment Data, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - 1996 Enrollment Data, 1996-1997 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Experimental Training Sessions for Supervisors and caseworkers, 1969 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Extended Study Program for the M.S.W. Degree, ca. 1976 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Faculty and Student Activities, Scholarship, Awards and Updates for Alumni Newsletter, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Faculty Recruitment - [RESTRICTED], 1990-1996; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Faculty Workload Policy Implementation - [RESTRICTED], 1992; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Fall 1988 and Spring 1989 Graduate and Undergraduate Course Offerings (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - 1988 - 1989 Family and Children Services Training catalog (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Field Instruction Manual, 1984 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Field Instruction Placements, 1971; 1975-1976; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Field Laboratory Course - Social Welfare Policy, Medicaid, and Social Work, 1972 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - 1988 Field Orientation, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Flyers, 1971-1972; 1974-1983; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Graduate Student Standing Committee Operating Procedures, 1981 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Grant Proposals, 1995-1997; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 25-29)
  - HEW Regulations on Protection of Human Subjects, 1973 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - 1991-1992 Human Diversity Committee, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Information on Course Offerings, 1979-1980 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Internal Evaluation Report, 1973 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Introduction to Research Methodology Course Materials, 1971; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Joint M.S.W. Program at Utica/Rome, 1993; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 35-36)
  - Master of Social Work Program Fields of Study in Direct Practice, 1985 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Master's Degree Program in Rehabilitation Counseling, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Max Siporin Lecture and Reception, 1995; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - May 1988 Professional Development Program Consultant Report, 1997-1998 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Memorandum - The University's Involvement in Urban Affairs and the Role of the School of Social Welfare, 1968 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Minority Membership on Social Agency Boards in the Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area, 1972 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Patricia Roberts Harris Public Service Fellowship, 1991; 1993 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - PEW Roundtable, 1995-1997; Undated (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Ph. D. Program in Social Welfare, 1983-1986 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Planning Meetings, 1988-1990; Undated (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Policy Manual, 1970-1974; Undated (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8-9)
  - Program Data, 1974 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Program Options for the M.S.W. Degree, 1984-1988; Undated (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Program Status - School of Social Welfare, 1974 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - 1987 - 1988 Progress Report on 1987 - 1992 Five Year Plan (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - 1988 - 1989 Progress Report on 1987 - 1992 Five Year Plan (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Progress Reports, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Proposal for a Bachelor of Science Major in Social Welfare, 1970 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Proposal for a Ph. D. in Social Welfare, 1970; Undated (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 17-18)
  - Proposal for the Master's Degree Program in Social Work, ca. 1965 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Proposed Center for Research on Social Work Practice, 1985-1987 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Presidential Award for Undergraduate Research, 1990-1991; 1993-1995 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Presidential Fellowship Award, 1986-1987 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - President's Undergraduate Leadership Awards, 1990-1991; 1993; 1995 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Quantitative Methods Interest Group, 1992-1997 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Questionnaire to Graduates of Social Work Programs Returning to Professional Practice, 1970 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Report of the State Needs Task Group on Social Services, 1992 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Report on Task Force on Public Affairs and Policy - Education, Research, and Service, 1981 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Report on Teleconferencing in categorical Determination, 1987 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Research Colloquium in Honor of the First Graduating Class, 1967 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Research Funding Data, 1988-1990 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Research in Social Work, 1980 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 31-32)
  - Resource Notebook for Group and Community Concepts - SSW 624, Undated (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Rockefeller College Distinguished Dissertation Award, 1990 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - 1984 - 1989 Rockefeller College Five Year Plan (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - 1985 - 1990 Rockefeller College Five Year Plan (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - 1987 - 1992 Rockefeller College Five Year Plan, 1986-1987; Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - 1990 - 1994 Rockefeller College Five Year Plan (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller College Five Year Plan - Planning Documents, 1981-1984; Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller College Planning Memoranda Prepared for President Swygert, 1991 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - School of Social Welfare Description, 1991; 1993-1997 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - School of Social Welfare Communications, 1964-1984; Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - 1990-1994 School of Social Welfare Five Year Plan, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - 1990-1994 School of Social Welfare Five Year Plan Revisions, Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8-9)
  - School of Social Welfare Profile, 1991; Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - 1981 - 1983 School of Social Welfare Three Year Plan - [RESTRICTED], 1978-1981; Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11-12)
  - 1982 -1984 School of Social Welfare Three Year Plan, 1981; Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13-14)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1992-1996 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook Materials, 1990-1992; Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16-17)
  - Scrapbook Photos, 1989; Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - 1974 Select Committee Report - School of Social Welfare Response, 1974-1975; Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 19-20)
  - Service Delivery by State and Local Governments: case Problems and Commentary, 1977 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Social Characteristics Data Profile - 27 Upstate Counties, 1976 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Social Service Task Force Draft Data Collection Plan, 1992 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Social Service Task Force Educational Program Data, 1992 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24-25)
  - Social Service Task Force Final Data Collection Plan, 1992 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Social Service Task Force Focus Group Reports, 1992 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 27-28)
  - Social Service Task Force Meeting Dates, 1992 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Social Trends Data, 1988-1993; 1995-1996 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 30-31)
  - A Social Welfare Paper - A Brief History of the Current Public Welfare Crisis, 1969 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - A Social Welfare Paper - Is there a Manpower Crisis in Social Work? / Need there be a Manpower Crisis in Social Welfare?, 1969 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - A Social Welfare Paper - Supervision: The Why and the Wherefore, 1970 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - A Social Welfare Paper - The Application of Social System Theory to Social Work in Family Diagnosis and Treatment, 1969 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - A Social Welfare Paper - The Social Services: Next Steps After Public Assistance, 1969 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Social Welfare School and Program Descriptions, 1988; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Social Work Data, 1991-1992; 1994-1995; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Social Work Licensure, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Social Work Licensure Exam Results, 1972; 1976; 1978-1979; 1991; Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)